Welcome back to the arena. You've completed your preseason conditioning. You looked inward,
you gathered the intel, you created your inner blueprint. You now have the raw materials,
your values, your strengths, your key experiences. This will shape how you not only win from
within, but it will shape how you begin to show up to those around you. Now today we move from
reviewing the game tape to drafting the playbook. We'll take the intel from your personal scouting
report and use it to design the single most important tool for your leadership. Your M.V.P.
blueprint, which stands for your mission, vision, purpose, and values. After you've architected your
M.V.P., I'm going to introduce you to the performance system that will bring it all to life, the 90-day
way. This isn't about writing a purpose statement for a slide deck. It's about building your
strategic operating system that scales your leadership. This lesson is about building your
game plan. The A.R.A.W. pillars we are conditioning today are alignment and agility. Let's get to work.